https://www.ppadv.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
PlansPlansOne-to-One AdvisorsLeadership RetreatOne-to-One AdvisorsSales AppsGeo PixelP2 PixelExitGadgetRev-up ToolkitsAboutAboutWhat people have to sayResourcesHard FactsThink Tank TuesdayAsk PotratzBlogSubscribeContact518-788-4724
518-631-5505Digital Web and Mobile Privacy StatementPOTRATZ Marketing is committed to respecting your privacy. This privacy statement governs the collection and use of information collected through this website and other POTRATZ digital properties.Information Gathering and Use of InformationPersonally Identifiable InformationPOTRATZ will not collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit our websites or digital properties unless you voluntarily provide us with that information.
POTRATZ may request personally identifiable information from you if you wish, for example, to access a password-protected website, join a mailing list, or engage in a payment transaction.
POTRATZ may use that information for such purposes as fulfilling your requests for our information or services, communication information that may be of interest to you, and conducting research surveys.
POTRATZ will not share your information with third parties except as set forth below under “Sharing Your Information.”Non-Personally Identifiable InformationWhen you visit POTRATZ websites and other POTRATZ digital properties, we may automatically collect and store information sent by your web browser, such as IP addresses (i.e., the Internet address of your computer) in server logs. We also collect standard information about your computer (such as your web browser and operating system) and about your usage of our websites and digital properties (such as pages visited, length of visit, and search queries).
This information, which does not identify your personally, is aggregated and used to help diagnose problems and suggest points for improving parts of our website and digital properties. For example, we utilize statistical software to identify which parts of our website are most heavily used and which portion of our audience comes from within the POTRATZ network of websites.CookiesLike many other websites, portions of POTRATZ’s websites and digital properties may use cookies.
Cookies are text files that may be transferred to your computer or mobile device through your web browsing software. These cookies are used to remember your preferences or to track statistics on usage of various portions of POTRATZ websites and digital properties. Our use of cookies does not involve the collection of personally identifiable information.You can choose not to accept cookies by selection settings on your web browser that block or restrict the use of cookies. You can also delete cookies that have been placed on your computer or device.For more information about the use of cookies by third parties, see below under “Behavioral Advertising.”Sharing Your InformationIn cases when POTRATZ has personally identifiable information (PII) about you, we will not sell, rent, or share that PII in accordance with any state laws and regulations.Behavioral AdvertisingPOTRATZ may contract with third party vendors to show our advertisements on non-POTRATZ websites and digital properties. POTRATZ and third party vendors with whom we contract may use cookies and web beacons to serve our ads based on your prior visit(s) to POTRATZ websites and digital properties and to assess the effectiveness of our ads. This is also called Targeted Advertising or Interest-Based Advertising.These techniques use only non-personally identifiable information, and you may opt out of behavioral advertising by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page at https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.SecurityPOTRATZ has implemented reasonable physical, technical, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure all information we collect online against loss, misuse, or alteration of the information under our control. This includes the use of encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Please note that while we work hard to protect the security of your information, POTRATZ cannot provide an absolute guarantee as to the security of any information you transmit through our websites or digital properties, and that you do so at your own risk.Third Party SitesPOTRATZ websites and digital properties may link to external sites that are not controlled by POTRATZ. Your use of such websites will be subject to the privacy statements of those websites, which we encourage you to read. POTRATZ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and does not make any representations about them.AddendumThis site is being monitored by one or more third-party monitoring software(s), and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service. You may control the data being collected from your visit by visiting https://smart-pixl.com through a universal consumer options page located at https://smart-pixl.com/Unsub/unsub.html.Changes to this Privacy StatementWe reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement in whole or in part at any time. The modified policy will be posted on this page with an updated effective date.QuestionsIf you have questions about this Privacy Statement or the privacy practices of POTRATZ websites or digital properties, please contact support@ppadv.com.Effective Date: Jan 1, 2019See strategies we’ve shared
Subscribe for more business growth strategies.
Subscribe
TALK TO US518-788-4724sales@ppadv.com31 Lafayette Street, Schenectady, New York, 12305EXPLOREAboutContactCareersResources Terms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicySitemapFOLLOW US
© 2020 POTRATZSubscribe to receive actionable strategies and insider knowledge.
LeadershipEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
0
